ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NAFTA- Reports on Mexico, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- NAFTA Negotiations, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 2)
- NAFTA Negotiations, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 3)
- NAFTA Articles, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 4)
- NAFTA Articles, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 5)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance for Dislocated Workers, 1991 (Box 195, Folder 6)
- NAFTA Implementation Legislation, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 7)
- NAFTA Notes, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 8)
- NAFTA Public Hearings, 1991 (Box 195, Folder 9)
- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 10)
- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 11)
- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 12)
- Textile, Apparel and Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 195, Folder 13)
- Textile, Apparel and Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 195, Folder 14)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  [Folder 1 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  [Folder 2 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  [Folder 3 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  [Folder 4 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  [Folder 5 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  [Folder 6 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  [Folder 7 of 8]
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  [Folder 8 of 8]
- FFACT Statements, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 9)
- FFACT Statements, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 10)
- FFACT Statements, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 11)
- Antidumping Reform, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Economic Consulting Services Statements, 1994 (Box 197, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Market Close-up Report, 1991 (Box 197, Folder 3)
- US-Mexico Free Trade Negotiations, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 4)
- US-Mexico Free Trade Negotiations, 1991 (Box 197, Folder 5)
- Speech Materials, 1980-1986 (Box 197, Folder 6)
- Speech Materials, 1980-1986 (Box 197, Folder 7)
- Strike Authorizations, 1988-1991 (Box 197, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens- General, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens- Settlement, 1980 (Box 197, Folder 10)
- Subsidies Code, 1980 (Box 197, Folder 11)
- Suit Import Committee, 1981 (Box 197, Folder 12)
- Sweater Dumping Code, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 13)
- Sweatshop Campaign, 1996 (Box 197, Folder 14)
- Swimwear Documents, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 15)
- Target Sportswear Labels, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 16)
- Target Corporation Policies, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 17)
- Textiles Surveillance Body, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 18)
- Tender Offers- Wirth, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 19)
- Tariff- Trade Negotiations, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 1)
- Tariff Acceleration, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 2)
- Textile Bill, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 3)
- Textile Bill, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 4)
- Textile Bill, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 5)
- Tent Imports, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 6)
- Textiles- Labor Department (Box 198, Folder 7)
- Textiles General, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 8)
- Textile Exports, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 9)
- Textile White Paper: Administrative Textile Program, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 10)
- Textile Labeling Bill: Committee on Commerce and Energy, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 11)
- Textile Division: American Textile Manufacturers Institute, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 12)
- Textile/Apparel Industry: Congressional Textile Caucus, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 13)
- International Trade in Textiles, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 14)
- Textile Bill, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 15)
- Textile Bill, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 16)
- Statistics Industry: Clothing Manufacturers of America, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 17)
- Statistics Industry: International Trade Commission, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 18)
- Statistics Industry: International Trade Commission, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 19)
- Speech Materials: Economic Policy Institute, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 20)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 199, Folder 1)
- Textile Bill: Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 2)
- Textile Bill: Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 3)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 199, Folder 4)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 199, Folder 5)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 199, Folder 6)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 199, Folder 7)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 199, Folder 8)
- Textile Bill: FFACT, 1985 (Box 199, Folder 9)
- Textile Bill: US Textile and Apparel, 1985 (Box 200, Folder 1)
- Textile Bill: US Textile and Apparel, 1985 (Box 200, Folder 2)
- Trade Bill: Trade Reform Action Coalition, 1987 (Box 200, Folder 3)
- Trade Policy: Cong. Florio, 1984 (Box 200, Folder 4)
- Subcommittee on International Trade Statements, 1982 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Trade Bill Reform Initiative, 1985 (Box 200, Folder 6)
- International Trade Correspondence, 1987 (Box 200, Folder 7)
- Trade Agreement Acts, 1984 (Box 200, Folder 8)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance Suit, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 9)
- House Trade Bill: Worker Rights Provisions, 1985 (Box 200, Folder 10)
- Trade Bill: Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 11)
- Harvard University Shirt Seminar Notes, 1991 (Box 200, Folder 12)
- Warnacoo Group Inc. Statements, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 13)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Aug. 3-4, 1993) (Box 201, Folder 13)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (May 4-5, 1993) (Box 201, Folder 12)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Feb. 15-18, 1993) (Box 201, Folder 11)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Nov. 5, 1992) (Box 201, Folder 10)
- 1992 General Board Meeting (AFL-CIO; September 3, 1992) (Box 201, Folder 9)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Aug. 4-5, 1992) (Box 201, Folder 8)
- Statement by AFL-CIO, Executive Council (Aug. 4, 1992) (Box 201, Folder 7)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Feb. 17-20, 1992) (Box 201, Folder 6)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (May 8, 1991) (Box 201, Folder 5)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Feb. 18-22, 1991) (Box 201, Folder 4)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (July 31-Aug. 1, 1990) (Box 201, Folder 3)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (May 23-24, 1990) (Box 201, Folder 2)
- Minutes: Executive Council. AFL-CIO (Feb. 19-22, 1990) (Box 201, Folder 1)